[音乐]
[MUSIC]
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：JavaScript函数具有return语句return语句
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: JavaScript functions have return statements return statement
停止函数的执行，将控制权返回给调用者，并
stops the execution of the function returns control to the caller and
也可以选择返回值。
can also optionally return a value.
包含的RETURN语句可以采用表达式和
Return statement contained can take an expression and
将计算表达式，返回其值或
will evaluate the expression return its value or
您可以有一个不返回任何内容的RETURN语句。
you can have a return statement that returns nothing.
它实际上将返回值undefined或
It will actually return the value undefined or
如果函数落到底部，它将返回未定义的值。
if the function falls through the bottom, it will return the undefined value.
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：我建议您不要在循环中创建函数对象。
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: I recommend that you not make function objects in a loop.
它可能是浪费的，因为每个新的函数对象都是在
It can be wasteful, because every new function object is created on
每次迭代，所以可能会很昂贵。
every iteration, so that could be expensive.
它也可能会让人混淆，因为新函数在循环上闭合
It can also be confusing, because the new function closes over the loops
变量没有超过它们的当前值，这种混淆可能会导致错误。
variables not over their current values and that confusion can lead to bugs.
例如，这里我们有一个for循环，它将循环
For example, here we've got a for loop, which is going to loop over
一个div数组，它将向每个div添加一个单击处理程序，
an array of divs and it's gonna add a click handler to each one,
当点击它时，将警告div的id，并且
which when clicked on will alert the id of the div and
这段代码看起来非常简单，但它会失败。
this code looks very straightforward, but it will fail.
不管你点击哪个分区，它都会失败，
And the way it fails is no matter which div you click on,
它们都将显示相同的ID。
they will all display the same id.
这将是最后一个
It'll be the last one and
这是因为内部函数捕获的是
it's because what's being captured by the inner function is the current value of
div.id不是创建函数时div.id的值。
div.id not not the value of div.id the at the time that the function was created.
所以绕过这一点的方法是根本不使用四个循环，
So the way to get around that is to not use a four loop at all,
每个使用四个并将传入一个函数，
use four each and will pass in a function,
其将接收每个div作为参数并且将正确地提醒。
which will receive each div of as an argument and will alert correctly.
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：我们调用带有配对后缀运算符的函数，
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: We invoke functions with the pairing suffix operator,
它将包含零个或多个逗号分隔的参数，并且
which will surround zero or more comma separated arguments and
这些参数中的每一个都将绑定到函数的一个参数。
each of those arguments will be bound to one of the parameters of the function.
如果使用太多参数调用函数，
If a function is called with too many arguments,
忽略额外的参数。
the extra arguments are ignored.
这不是错误。
It is not an error.
如果调用参数的参数太少，
If an argument is called with too few arguments,
缺少的值将是未定义的值。
the missing values will be the undefined value.
如果没有对参数、其类型或
If there is no explicit type checking on the arguments, on their types or
在他们的数字上。
on their numbers.
所以如果你真的关心那些东西，你需要自己去检查。
So if you really care about that stuff, you need to check it yourself.
一般来说，你不需要这样做。
Generally, you don't have to.
事实证明，JavaScript中的大多数默认值都是正确的。
It turns out most of the defaults in JavaScript are right.
所以如果你不检查，它通常会做正确的事情。
So that if you don't do checking, it'll usually do the right thing anyway.
所以除了正式定义为函数一部分的任何参数之外，
So in addition to any parameters that are formally defined as part of a function,
还有两个额外的伪参数，您也可以访问它们
there are also two bonus pseudo parameters that you can also get access
争论和这个。
to arguments and this.
我不推荐使用它们中的任何一个，但是
I don't recommend using either of them, but
他们在语言中都很受欢迎。
they're both very popular in the language.
所以，我需要描述他们两个。
So, I'd need to describe them both.
我将从论点开始。
I will start with the arguments.
当调用函数时，除了其参数外，它还会获得一个特殊的
When a function is invoked in addition to its parameters, it also gets a special
打印机调用了参数，它包含来自调用的所有参数。
printer called arguments and it contains all of the arguments from the invocation.
所以在parens中传递的所有内容都被称为函数，
So everything that got passed in the parens are called the function,
这些值中的每一个都将在参数组中。
every one of those values will be in the arguments array.
现在参数组的一个问题是，它不是真正的数组，
Now one problem with the arguments array is, it is not really an array,
即使是以JavaScript认为数组的奇怪方式。
even in the weird way that JavaScript thinks of arrays.
它是一个类似数组对象。
It is an array like object.
它是一个具有长度属性的对象，但它不是神奇的长度属性
It's an object that has a length property, but it's not a magical length property and
它没有继承任何有用的数组方法。
it doesn't inherit any of the useful array methods.
所以，这是一件很难处理的事情。
So, it's a difficult thing to work with.
您确实获得了参数dot length，这将是
You do get arguments dot length, which will be the number of arguments that were
实际上通过了，并且与参数之间有一个奇怪的交互。
actually passed and there's a weird interaction with the parameters.
因此，如果将参数更改为零以下，则第一个参数也会更改。
So if you change arguments sub zero, the first parameter also changes.
如果更改第二个参数，则参数sub 1将更改为
If you change the second parameter, then argument sub one changes for
制作JavaScript引擎的人。
the people who make JavaScript engines.
这可能是语言中最令人讨厌的特性，
This is maybe the most hated feature of the language,
因为他们真的很努力想让它走得更快
cuz they're working really hard to try to make it go fast and
当你必须处理像那样的行为时，你不能走得太快。
you can't go fast when you have to mess with behavior like that.
所以，让我给你展示一个如何使用它的例子。
So, let me show you an example of how you could use it.
所以我们得到了一个简单的SUM函数，它将接收一些可变数量的
So we've got a simple sum function, which will receive some variable number of
数字，它会将它们相加并返回总数。
numbers and it will add them up and return the total.
因此，我们将从长度和
So, we're going to get from arguments that length and
我们要添加的东西的数量。
the number of things that we're going to add.
我们会循环进去，我们会得到每一个论点，
We're gonna loop through in and we're gonna get each of those arguments,
并将其加到总和中。
and add it to the total.
注意，我没有在一些中包含任何参数，因为我不需要，我可以这样做。
Notice I didn't include any parameters in some, cuz I didn't need to I could have.
但这并不是必须的，因为我从争论中获得了所有的材料。
But it wasn't necessary, because I'm getting all the material from arguments.
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：所以现在这真的是一件很难做到的事情
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: So now this is a really difficult thing to have
在任何一种语言中，因为它使语言很难谈论。
in any language, because it makes the language hard to talk about.
这就像是与Abbott和Costello结对编程。
It's like pair programming with Abbott and Costello.
所以，请容忍我。
So, bear with me.
因此，this参数包含对调用对象的引用。
So, the this parameter contains a reference to the object of invocation.
这允许方法知道它与什么对象相关。
This allows a method to know what object it is concerned with.
这允许单个函数对象为多个对象提供服务，并且
This allows a single function object to service many objects and
这是原型遗传的关键。
it's the key to prototypal inheritance.
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：在JavaScript中有四种调用函数的方法。
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: There are four ways to call a function in JavaScript.
函数形式，方法形式，构造函数形式和应用形式，
The function form, method form, constructor form and apply form,
四种形式。
four forms.
我认为在一个设计良好的语言中，应该有一种形式，但是
I think in a well-designed language, there should be one form, but
我们有四个，它们的不同之处在于发生了什么。
we've got four and the way they vary is in what happens to this.
因此，让我们从方法表单开始。
So, let's start with the method form.
我们说，方法形成了一些对象点方法名称或
The method form, we say, some object dot method name or
一些对象括号，计算结果为方法名的表达式。
some object bracket, an expression that evaluates to a method name.
当我们以这种方式调用一个函数时，它将被绑定到这个对象上。
When we call a function this way, then this will get bound to this object.
它允许被调用的方法知道它将指向哪个对象
It allows the method that gets called to know which object it's going to
操控。
be manipulating.
在大多数语言中，绑定发生得相当晚，但是
In most languages, the binding of this happens fairly late, but
没有人比JavaScript更晚做这件事。
nobody does it as late as JavaScript.
Java脚本直到调用的那一刻才绑定它，
Java Script doesn't bind this until the moment of invocation,
然后是函数形式，看起来是一样的，
then there's the function form, which looks the same,
只是我们没有对象前缀。
except we don't have an object prefix.
所以，我们只有一些函数值，我们称之为。
So, we just have some function value and we call that.
在这种情况下，这会被反弹到全局对象。
In this case, this gets bounced to the global object.
它是所有全局变量的容器
It's the thing that is the container of all the global variables and
这是一件可怕的事情，因为它泄漏了太多的能力。
that's a terrible thing, because it's leaking way too much capability.
这是一种安全风险，这是一种可靠性风险。
It's a security hazard, it's a reliability hazard.
这是在ES5/严格模式下修复的。
This was sort of fixed in ES5/Strict mode.
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：但不完全是。
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: But not completely.
在ES5/Strict模式下，这将绑定到undefined。
In ES5/Strict mode, this gets bound to undefined.
所以至少我们没有把它和危险的东西绑在一起，
So at least we're not binding it to something dangerous,
但有时也不是你想要的。
but sometimes it's not what you want either.
如果你在一个方法内部有一个内部函数，
That if you have an inner function inside of a method,
您希望内部函数帮助该方法完成其工作。
you want the inner function to help the method do its work.
但是内部函数没有看到这个，
But the inner function doesn't get to see this,
因为内部函数作为函数调用。
because the inner function gets called as a function.
因此，这将要么是全局对象，要么是未定义的。
And so, it's this will be either the global object or undefined.
因此解决方法是在外部函数中，在方法中，
So the workaround is in the outer function, in the method,
您创建一个名为的变量，将其赋值给它，然后
you create a variable called that assign this to it and
然后内部函数可以看到这一点。
then the inner function gets to see that.
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：然后有一个构造函数形式，
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Then there is a constructor form,
它看起来像函数形式，只是有一个新的前缀。
it looks like the function form, except there is a new prefix.
并且当用新的前缀调用函数时，
And when a function is called with a new prefix,
将创建一个新对象，并将其绑定到该对象。
a new object is created and will be bound to this.
并且如果构造函数没有显式返回值，
And if the constructor function does not have an explicit return value,
那么这将是返回值并且
then this will be the return value and
这是用在伪古典风格，这将在几分钟内到达。
this is used in the pseudo classical style, which will get to in a few minutes.
最后是申请表。
And finally, there is the apply form.
在Apply表单中，调用Function对象的Apply方法，并
In the apply form, you call the apply method of the function object and
您可以指定它的值。
you get to specify what the value of this is going to be.
此外，还可以提供参数组或
In addition, you can also provide either an array of arguments or
您可以提供用逗号分隔的单个参数。
you can provide individual arguments separated by commas.
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：总之，有四种调用形式，函数，
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: So to summarize, there are four invocation forms, function,
方法、构造函数和应用。
method, constructor and apply.
它们各自根据它们对此所做的事情而有所不同。
They each vary according to what they do with this.
再一次，我不推荐使用这个，但这就是大多数
And again, I don't recommend using this at all, but that's how most
人们使用这种语言，几分钟后我将向您展示另一种语言。
people use the language and I'll show you an alternative in a few minutes.
所以，你们都知道递归。
So, you all know about recursion.
这就是当你有一个用自身定义的函数或者
That's when you have a function that is defined in terms of itself or
可以称自己为非常重要的东西。
the can call itself really, really important thing.
我不需要告诉你什么是快速排序，
I don't need to tell you about Quicksort,
这是使用递归的一个重要示例。
that's one of the important examples of using recursion.
JavaScript有一个递归，这很好。
JavaScript has a recursion, which is good.
如果您不熟悉递归函数，
If you're not familiar with recursive functions, I highly,
强烈推荐一本名为“小李斯珀”的书，这本书已经过修订。
highly recommend a book called The Little Lisper, which has been revised.
现在叫做小阴谋家。
It's now called the Little Schemer.
它是基于Scheme语言的，但它实际上并不是关于Scheme的。
It's based on the Scheme language, but it's not really about scheme.
它是关于递归函数，这本书中的所有内容都可以用
It's about recursive functions and everything in that book can be written in
JavaScript和此网页将为您提供进行翻译的关键。
JavaScript and this web page will give you the key to to doing that translation.
强烈推荐。
Highly, highly recommended.
这是一本可以显著改变你的思维方式的书
This is one of those books that can significantly change the way you think in
一种非常好的方式。
a really good way.
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：还有一本书叫做
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: There's another book called The Principles of
编程语言由RC Tennent和
Programming Languages by RC Tennent and
他的原则之一是通信原则
one of his principles is the principle of correspondence in which he
讨论变量在某些语言中如何与参数相似。
talks about how variables are like parameters in some languages.
所以在这里，我们有两个版本的阶乘函数和
So here, we have two versions of the factorial function and
其中一个结果是变量，另一个结果是参数。
one of them result is a variable and the other the result is a parameter.
否则，这两个函数的作用完全相同。
Otherwise, these two functions do exactly the same thing.
因此，这证明了变量和
And so, this demonstrates the similarity of variables and
基于函数构造方式的参数。
parameters based on how the function is constructed.
关于第二个函数的有趣之处是，
The interesting thing about the second function is,
它使用了一个可立即撤销的函数表达式。
it's using an immediately revocable function expression.
所以在这里，我们有一个函数，声明或表达式的函数，这就是
So here, we have a function, declaration or function of expression, which is
创建一个新的Function对象，然后我们立即调用它并传入一个。
creating a new function object, which we then call immediately passing in the one.
所以一般来说，我们可以取任何表达式
So in general, we can take any expression and
将其包装在一个函数中，该函数将返回表达式和
wrap it in a function that will return that expression and
立即调用函数，它与表达式做同样的事情。
call the function immediately and it does the same thing as expression.
它只是更冗长，但它做的是相同的事情。
It's just more verbose, but it does the same thing.
现在，事实证明这在JavaScript中并不适用于所有的值。
Now, turns out this is not true in JavaScript for all values.
例如，
For example,
当您将这些和参数放在不同的函数中时，它们的含义会发生变化。
these and arguments change their meaning when you put them in a different function.
所以它不适用于他们，但它适用于
So it doesn't work for them, but it works for
所有其他表达式，它适用于四个语句。
all other expressions and it works for four statements.
您可以将任意一组语句放在一个函数中，然后
You can take any bunch of statements and put them in a function and
立即打电话，它说，虽然，你已经执行了那些语句，
call immediately and it's says, though, you had executed those statements,
除了var函数break continue和
except that var function break continue and
当您将它们放入另一个函数中时，return会更改它们的含义。
return change their meaning when you put them in another function.
否则，您可以进行这种转换，并且有一些有趣的
Otherwise, you can do this transformation and there are some interesting
由于能够做到这一点，可能会发生的事情。
things that can happen as a result of being being able to do this.
因此，这是您在函数式语言中寻找的特性。
So, this is a feature that you look for in a functional language.